CV Application

Vitaly Iromenko

Email: I.have.mail.in@gmail.com GitHub: https://github.com/druzver

LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/vitaly-yeromenko

iOS, Android Mobile Developer

About me

I position myself as a developer of native mobile applications, but also have enough knowledge in Java Script. About 10+ years of experience in commercial projects. Of which in mobile development for more than +7 years. Developed products in different languages JavaScript, Java, Kotlin, Swift, etc. I use JS for writing helper tools and backend. I know the full path of how to build an app, from scratch to the release in stores.

My goal is to participate in the creation of a useful product that people will use every day.

Main skils

- Android development: Kotlin, Java, Android Jetpack
- iOS Development: Swift, Cocoa
- Backend/Frontend development: Java Script, Coffee Script
- Databases: SQLite, PostgreSQL
- Release Markets: Google Play, Apple Store
- Mobile Tools/Platforms: Firebase, Heap

Communication languages

- Ukrainian native speaker
- Russian native speaker
- English somewhere between A2 (Pre Intermediate) B1 (Intermediate)

Experience

2015 - 2022 - Global Fleet Management Inc.

Role: Senior Mobile Developer

Responsibility: Developing mobile solutions for GPS tracking and vehicle driver tools. Released native(Kotlin, Swift) and hybrid (Cordova) applications. Work with Maps, Bluetooth, Video Streaming, etc.

2014 - 2015 - Made It []

Role: PHP Software Developer

Responsibility: Developing the solutions for the hosting provider platform.

2010 - 2014 - Regional Center of Informatization (Government Company)

Role: Senior Software Developer

Responsibilities: Develop tools for the regional government. Using PHP and JavaScript

2008-2009 - Bank "Family"

Role: Database Developer

Responsibilities: Support and extend banking tools by writing DB

extensions and SQL requests

Education

Donetsk State Institute of Artificial IntelligenceDonetsk State Institute of Artificial Intelligence

Software engineering